Privacy Policy
==============

Please read the following terms of the Privacy Policy which describes how we protect the privacy of our users. We take great care so that every user of our service feels safe.

Our role is to make the telecommunications network and resources available to users, so that users can freely add and comment on business phone numbers for their own personal purposes. Please, keep in mind that we do not check the additions of numbers or their user feedback.

We treat cookie files and IP numbers of users in accordance with the rules described below. If you make use of the service, it means that you fully agree with the rules.

**What are cookies / cookie files?**

Cookies are sent to search engines and stored in the device memory and read by our servers once you connect with the Service. We guarantee that the files contain no information that could allow Your identification by third parties. They also do not allow third parties to get to know your personal data, or to contact you by email. They do not allow third parties to access your private aircraft.

Cookies are text files stored on your computer, and accessible only to sites that create them. Our website may occasionally use cookies and log files for statistical analysis, to understand user behavior, administer the site, to tailor information presented to a user based on their preferences, and improve the user experience. Any information collected by our use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate anonymous basis. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can delete or disable cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://scamphone.co.uk. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to http://scamphone.co.uk and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html

**How can you disable the processing of cookie files?**

Please keep in mind that it is only because of cookie files and advertising that our service can get better every time you use it. Through your search engine (browser) settings You can decide whether cookies files should be treated or not. If you do not want cookie files to be processed, you must disable the processing by selecting an appropriate option in the settings of your serach engine (browser) for privacy. If you disable the processing of cookie files, it will not affect how the service is displayed. If you want to disable Google Analytics, you must download and install a special plug-in (it is available for the following search engines: Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, Opera, Microsoft Internet Explorer) or disable the processing file cookie service in your search engine (browser).

**How we treat IP numbers?**

Each time you use our service, add a number or leave a comment, we read the IP number of your network, but, by default, we do not permanently store the data to make it accessible to the public.

However, if we encounter mails of IP numbers are stored permanently by us and added to a blacklist. We treat the content as spam whenever numbers or comments are added to the service by an IP number in the time period that is too short for a human to do or when we receive credible or official notification on the unlawful nature of the data added using the IP number.

About ScamPhone.co.uk
---------------------

ScamPhone.co.uk is primarily a community-powered website where users submit the experience they have had with a phone number. To help them start, the website offers some initial information about the phone number. The information that users share about a phone number is shared with other users. helps build a directory containing phone numbers, their details, and public opinions on those numbers.

© 2016-2023 scamphone.co.uk   [Home](http://www.scamphone.co.uk/) / [Privacy Policy](http://www.scamphone.co.uk/privacy) / [Terms of Use](http://www.scamphone.co.uk/terms) / [About Us](http://www.scamphone.co.uk/about) / [Contact](http://www.scamphone.co.uk/contact)

[](http://statcounter.com/ "real time web
analytics")
